Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
♪Fade like drifting clouds♪
♪تتلاشى مثل السحب المنجرفة♪
♪Half dream, half illusion♪
♪نصف حلم، ونصف وهم♪
♪Fated or fleeting♪
♪مقدر أو عابر♪
♪Spring breeze falls from my brow♪
♪نسائم الربيع تهب من جبهتي♪
♪Where to go, I do not know♪
♪أين أذهب، لا أعرف♪
♪I turn, and all is gone♪
♪أتحول، وكل شيء قد ذهب♪
♪Ask how deep the dust of love runs♪
♪اسأل عن مدى عمق غبار الحب♪
♪How strong longing grows♪
♪ما أشد الشوق الذي ينمو♪
♪I play till the final note♪
♪ألعب حتى النغمة الأخيرة♪
=In The Name of Loyalty=
=باسم الولاء=
=Episode 21=
=الحلقة 21=
Gao Ji thinks my brother
غاو جي يعتقد أن أخي
hates my guts.
يكره أحشائي.
He'd never believe I'd
لن يصدق أبدًا أنني سأفعل ذلك
bring him to the palace.
أحضره إلى القصر.
That's called hiding in plain sight.
هذا ما يسمى بالاختباء أمام أعيننا.
Now,
الآن،
Gao Ji is
جاو جي هو
focused on preparing the banquet,
ركزت على إعداد المأدبة،
and meanwhile,
وفي هذه الأثناء،
searching the city for Shi Nan.
البحث عن مدينة شي نان.
This is when the defenses are weakest.
هذا هو الوقت الذي تكون فيه الدفاعات أضعف.
We must contact trusted officials now
يجب علينا الاتصال بالمسؤولين الموثوق بهم الآن
to discuss our plan.
لمناقشة خطتنا.
However,
لكن،
no matter which path we take next,
بغض النظر عن المسار الذي نتخذه بعد ذلك،
our priority now is to reclaim the imperial seal.
أولويتنا الآن هي استعادة الختم الإمبراطوري.
Exactly.
بالضبط.
The seal is the core of power.
الختم هو جوهر القوة.
All memorials and military orders
جميع النصب التذكارية والأوامر العسكرية
require the seal and imperial rescript.
تتطلب الختم والمرسوم الإمبراطوري.
If we get the seal,
إذا حصلنا على الختم،
we essentially control the military.
نحن نسيطر بشكل أساسي على الجيش.
By then,
بحلول ذلك الوقت،
officials currently vacillating
المسؤولون مترددون حاليا
will recognize the shift in power.
سوف ندرك التحول في السلطة.
If Shi Yu reveals the seal,
إذا كشف شي يو عن الختم،
Gao Ji will lose
غاو جي سوف يخسر
his legitimate authority to deploy troops.
سلطته الشرعية في نشر القوات.
Gao Ji values
قيم جاو جي
his reputation most.
سمعته أكثر.
If he knows I possess the imperial seal,
إذا كان يعلم أنني أمتلك الختم الإمبراطوري،
he won't dare act recklessly.
لن يجرؤ على التصرف بتهور.
He might even
ربما حتى
lose his composure.
يفقد رباطة جأشه.
But Gao Ji already knows
لكن قاو جي يعرف بالفعل
you won't willingly be his puppet.
لن تكوني دمية في يده طوعا.
Therefore,
لذلك،
you must appear weak recently,
يجب أن تبدو ضعيفًا في الآونة الأخيرة،
and let him think
ودعه يفكر
you know limits,
أنت تعرف الحدود،
and will stay out of his way
وسوف تبقى خارج طريقه
under his control.
تحت سيطرته.
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
We'll lull Gao Ji into complacency,
سوف نخدع غاو جي حتى يصل إلى الرضا عن النفس،
and also urgently locate the imperial seal's hiding place.
وأيضا تحديد مكان إخفاء الختم الإمبراطوري بشكل عاجل.
(Minister Yin,)
(الوزير يين)
(gather all officials loyal to me)
(اجمع كل المسؤولين الموالين لي)
(to stage a performance in the court.)
(إقامة عرض في المحكمة.)
(General Yan,)
(الجنرال يان)
(to advance steadily,)
(للتقدم بثبات)
(I can only ask you all)
(لا أستطيع إلا أن أطلب منكم جميعا)
(to endure for now.)
(للتحمل في الوقت الراهن.)
(To destroy someone,)
(تدمير شخص ما)
(drive them mad first.)
(أجعلهم يجنون أولاً.)
(I'll be more obedient to the Prince Regent than ever.)
(سأكون أكثر طاعة للأمير الوصي من أي وقت مضى.)
(Of course,)
(بالطبع،)
(pain is necessary.)
(الألم ضروري.)
(I'll detain)
(سوف أحتجز)
(my trusted aides personally)
(مساعديني الموثوق بهم شخصيًا)
(to protect them)
(لحمايتهم)
(and preserve our strength.)
(وحفظ قوتنا.)
(It pains me,)
(إنه يؤلمني)
(but please endure a little longer.)
(ولكن من فضلك تحمل لفترة أطول قليلا.)
(Your Majesty, you've endured all this)
(يا صاحب الجلالة، لقد تحملت كل هذا)
(for a just court and a peaceful realm.)
(من أجل محكمة عادلة ومملكة سلمية.)
(I would die a thousand times without regret.)
(أود أن أموت ألف مرة دون ندم.)
(Everyone,)
(الجميع،)
(stick to the plan.)
(الالتزام بالخطة.)
(Yang Youxing, Minister of Rites,)
(يانغ يوشينغ، وزير الطقوس)
(has disregarded court laws)
(تجاهل قوانين المحكمة)
(and abused his power.)
(و اساء استعمال سلطته.)
(Imprison him immediately,)
(اسجنوه فوراً)
(pending trial and sentencing.)
(في انتظار المحاكمة والحكم.)
Shi Yu!
شي يو!
You heartless tyrant!
أيها الطاغية عديم القلب!
Move!
يتحرك!
What a tyrant!
يا له من طاغية!
My lord.
سيدي.
Why so many?
لماذا الكثير؟
Only one is true.
واحد فقط هو الصحيح.
What now?
ماذا الآن؟
I won't disturb your rest then.
لن أزعج راحتك إذن.
I'll come tomorrow.
سوف اتي غدا
You may return first.
يمكنك العودة أولاً.
It appears
يبدو أنه
the only time we can access the real seal
الوقت الوحيد الذي يمكننا فيه الوصول إلى الختم الحقيقي
is when Gao Ji carries it.
عندما يحملها غاو جي.
But if we try to steal it,
ولكن إذا حاولنا سرقتها،
Gao Ji would discover us
غاو جي سوف يكتشفنا
before we could escape.
قبل أن نتمكن من الهروب.
My lord,
سيدي،
His Majesty has arrived.
لقد وصل جلالته.
Your Majesty, you visit so late.
جلالتك، لقد أتيت إلى هنا في وقت متأخر جدًا.
Is there any urgent business?
هل هناك أي عمل عاجل؟
Lord Father,
يا رب الأب،
I was preparing my wedding banquet speech.
كنت أقوم بإعداد خطابي في حفل زفافي.
There are a few phrases
هناك بعض العبارات
I wish to consult you about.
أريد أن أستشيرك في هذا الأمر.
Your Majesty,
جلالتك،
how about I pay a visit to your chamber
ماذا عن أن أقوم بزيارة غرفتك؟
after tomorrow's court session?
بعد جلسة المحكمة غدا؟
It will only take a moment.
لن يستغرق الأمر سوى لحظة.
Lord Father.
يا رب الأب.
Prince Xiyou's wife
زوجة الأمير شيو
is my mother's cousin.
هو ابن عم والدتي.
Is this form of address appropriate?
هل هذا الشكل من الخطاب مناسب؟
Yes.
نعم.
That is the proper address.
هذا هو العنوان الصحيح .
What about this?
ماذا عن هذا؟
Are these addresses proper?
هل هذه العناوين صحيحة؟
The same.
نفس الشيء.
There are also a few details I'd...
هناك أيضًا بعض التفاصيل التي أود أن أذكرها.
Your Majesty,
جلالتك،
this seems rather presumptuous.
يبدو أن هذا متهور إلى حد ما.
Today's advice from you
نصيحه اليوم منك
exceeds ten years of study.
أكثر من عشر سنوات من الدراسة.
Guidance is appreciated. Please rest early.
شكرًا للإرشاد. يُرجى الراحة مبكرًا.
Now Gao Ji has left the capital to prepare the banquet,
الآن غادر غاو جي العاصمة لإعداد المأدبة،
we'll give him a grand welcome upon his return.
سنقدم له ترحيبا حارا عند عودته.
(The 26th day of the 10th lunar month)
(اليوم السادس والعشرون من الشهر القمري العاشر)
Soldiers, heed my command!
أيها الجنود، اتبعوا أوامري!
From now on,
من الآن فصاعدا،
the Imperial Guards,
الحرس الإمبراطوري،
Palace Guards,
حراس القصر،
Eastern Cavalry, and Western Cavalry
سلاح الفرسان الشرقي، وسلاح الفرسان الغربي
will be commanded by General Yan.
وسوف تكون تحت قيادة الجنرال يان.
The South Hawks Army will be led by Deputy Commander Zhang Mao.
سيكون جيش صقور الجنوب بقيادة نائب القائد تشانغ ماو.
Tiger Wing Army will be led by Deputy Commander Qin Bingkun.
سيكون جيش جناح النمر بقيادة نائب القائد تشين بينجكون.
All assume your posts immediately.
كل ما عليك فعله هو قبول مشاركاتك على الفور.
(Memorial tablet of Pingxiang people)
(لوحة تذكارية لشعب بينغشيانغ)
My lord, we...
سيدي نحن...
What's happening?
ماذا يحدث؟
By imperial decree,
بموجب مرسوم إمبراطوري،
Minister Chen Huan
الوزير تشين هوان
is convicted
تمت إدانته
of embezzling military funds.
اختلاس الأموال العسكرية.
Exiled to the frontier, effective immediately.
نُفي إلى الحدود، اعتبارًا من الآن.
Go!
يذهب!
(Memorial tablets)
(الألواح التذكارية)
By imperial decree,
بموجب مرسوم إمبراطوري،
Shen Kuo, the West General, who cares for the nation and its people,
شين كو، الجنرال الغربي، الذي يهتم بالأمة وشعبها،
is hereby cleared of all charges
تم تبرئته من جميع التهم
and reinstated to his former post.
وأعيد إلى منصبه السابق.
- Thank you, Your Majesty.
- شكرا لك يا جلالة الملك.
I, Shi Yu.
أنا، شي يو.
Shi Nan.
إنه هنا.
Cheng Ge.
تشنغ قه.
We shall engrave your grievances in my heart,
سننقش مظالمكم في قلبي،
- reclaim the realm,
- استعادة المملكة،
- and bring peace to the land.
- وأحل السلام في الأرض.
Stop! Stop the carriage!
قف! اوقف العربة!
My lord. My lord.
سيدي. سيدي.
Why aren't you at the palace?
لماذا لست في القصر؟
Why are you here?
لماذا انت هنا؟
The Western Cavalry, South Hawks Army
سلاح الفرسان الغربي، جيش صقور الجنوب
and Tiger Wing Army all have new commanders.
وجيش النمر والجناح لديهما قادة جدد.
Even the Imperial Guards,
حتى الحرس الامبراطوري،
Palace Guards,
حراس القصر،
and Eastern Cavalry
والفرسان الشرقيون
all answer to General Yan now.
كل الإجابة للجنرال يان الآن.
Nonsense!
هراء!
I still hold the imperial seal.
لا أزال أحمل الختم الإمبراطوري.
How could they obey?
كيف يمكنهم أن يطيعوا؟
Th-They said
ث-قالوا
the decree came directly from His Majesty,
لقد جاء المرسوم مباشرة من جلالته،
complete with imperial seal and imperial rescript.
كاملة مع الختم الإمبراطوري والمرسوم الإمبراطوري.
Please wait.
انتظر من فضلك.
You worthless fool.
أيها الأحمق الذي لا قيمة له.
Has one day apart
لديه يوم واحد منفصل
made you forget me?
هل جعلتك تنساني؟
Your Highness,
صاحب السمو،
without His Majesty's order, no one may enter.
بدون أمر جلالته، لا يجوز لأحد الدخول.
♪Without fate, this dream would fade♪
♪بدون القدر، هذا الحلم سوف يتلاشى♪
♪Without you, my life would quietly end♪
♪بدونك، حياتي ستنتهي بهدوء♪
♪Fade like drifting clouds♪
♪تتلاشى مثل السحب المنجرفة♪
♪Half dream, half illusion♪
♪نصف حلم، ونصف وهم♪
♪Fated or fleeting♪
♪مقدر أو عابر♪
♪Spring breeze falls from my brow♪
♪نسائم الربيع تهب من جبهتي♪
♪Where to go, I do not know♪
♪أين أذهب، لا أعرف♪
♪I turn, and all is gone♪
♪أتحول، وكل شيء قد ذهب♪
♪Ask how deep the dust of love runs♪
♪اسأل عن مدى عمق غبار الحب♪
♪How strong longing grows♪
♪ما أشد الشوق الذي ينمو♪
♪I play till the final note♪
♪ألعب حتى النغمة الأخيرة♪
♪Let fate cut like a blade♪
♪دع القدر يقطع مثل الشفرة♪
♪I bid you one last farewell♪
♪أقول لك وداعا أخيرا♪
♪I know not love's emptiness nor hatred's pain♪
♪لا أعرف فراغ الحب ولا ألم الكراهية♪
♪When we meet again, the snow will melt away♪
♪عندما نلتقي مرة أخرى، سوف يذوب الثلج♪
♪One vow, so deep in love♪
♪عهد واحد، عميق في الحب♪
♪I'd give my life for it♪
♪سأعطي حياتي من أجله♪